Guide to the Mix Collection, 1970-2014 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS.143
Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES IX: 1995, 118419
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files, 118738
    - Hospitality - Misc. correspondence and documents, 1995; 118762 (Box 7, Folder 703)
    - Legal - Signed curators' contracts, 1995; 118761 (Box 7, Folder 704)
    - Legal - PopSmear contract, 1995; 118760 (Box 7, Folder 705)
    - Letterhead - Fax cover sheets (blank), 1995; 118759 (Box 7, Folder 706)
    - Mailing lists - Filmmakers, 1995; 118758 (Box 8, Folder 707)
    - Mailing lists - Staff and committee, 1995; 118757 (Box 8, Folder 708)
    - Mailing lists - Press, 1995; 118756 (Box 8, Folder 709)
    - Mailing lists - Rolodex, 1995; 118755 (Box 8, Folder 710)
    - Notes - Budgets - Black Nation/Queer Nations?, 1995; 118754 (Box 8, Folder 711)
    - Notes - Budgets - Festival, 1995; 118753 (Box 8, Folder 712)
    - Notes - Mix Festival (general), 1995; 118752 (Box 8, Folder 713)
    - Notes - Party research, 1995; 118751 (Box 8, Folder 714)
    - Notes - Press research, 1995; 118750 (Box 8, Folder 715)
    - Notes - Press screenings/sponsorship, 1995; 118749 (Box 8, Folder 716)
    - Notes - Volunteers, 1995; 118748 (Box 8, Folder 717)
    - Notes - misc., 1995; 118747 (Box 8, Folder 718)
    - Postal - Bulk mail information, 1995; 118746 (Box 8, Folder 719)
    - Postal - Mix envelopes, 1995; 118745 (Box 8, Folder 720)
    - Programming - Selection process, film lists with scores, 1995; 118744 (Box 8, Folder 721)
    - Programming - Selection process, film lists with scores, 1995; 118743 (Box 8, Folder 722)
    - Programming - Scheduling, guest curators' programs, 1995; 118742 (Box 8, Folder 723)
    - Programming - Program guide, 1995; 118741 (Box 8, Folder 724)
    - Programming - Program listings, 1995; 118740 (Box 8, Folder 725)
    - Programming - Schedules, 1995; 118739 (Box 8, Folder 726)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence, 118730
    - Correspondence from filmmakers and film/arts organizations, 1995; 118737 (Box 8, Folder 727)
    - Correspondence - Shari Frilot, 1995; 118736 (Box 8, Folder 728)
    - Correspondence - Afterparties, 1995; 118735 (Box 8, Folder 729)
    - Correspondence - Bavo Defurne, 1995; 118734 (Box 8, Folder 730)
    - Correspondence - Free Speech TV, 1995; 118733 (Box 8, Folder 731)
    - Correspondence - Joshua Gamson (contains sociology paper on Mix, "Show Me Yours: Negotiating Collective Identity in Lesbian and Gay Film Festivals;" rebuttal paper from Sarah Schulman, "A Samoan Talks Back to Margaret Mead;" correspondence from Gamson to Schulman), 1995; 118732 (Box 8, Folder 732)
    - Correspondence - Rejection letter, 1995; 118731 (Box 8, Folder 733)
  - Subseries C: Entry Forms/Press Kits (see also Oversize series), 118692
    - Entry forms - 100 Years of Sodomy program, 1995; 118729 (Box 8, Folder 734)
    - Entry forms - Black Nations/Queer Nations? program, 1995; 118728 (Box 8, Folder 735)
    - Entry forms - Chill Out/Dont Rhine installation, 1995; 118727 (Box 8, Folder 736)
    - Entry forms - Close Encounters program, 1995; 118726 (Box 8, Folder 737)
    - Entry forms - Cybertopia program, 1995; 118725 (Box 8, Folder 738)
    - Entry forms - Demons program, 1995; 118724 (Box 8, Folder 739)
    - Entry forms - Desire in the Urban Landscape program, 1995; 118723 (Box 8, Folder 740)
    - Entry forms - Divas in Training program, 1995; 118722 (Box 8, Folder 741)
    - Entry forms - Drag Explosion program (DISK INCLUDED), 1995; 118721 (Box 8, Folder 742)
    - Entry forms - Fagsploitation, Baby! program, 1995; 118720 (Box 8, Folder 743)
    - Entry forms - Generation Sex program, 1995; 118719 (Box 8, Folder 744)
    - Entry forms - Girls Girls Girls program, 1995; 118718 (Box 8, Folder 745)
    - Entry forms - History program, 1995; 118717 (Box 8, Folder 746)
    - Entry forms - Hot 'n' Sticky program, 1995; 118716 (Box 8, Folder 747)
    - Entry forms - Hot off the Cutting Board program, 1995; 118715 (Box 8, Folder 748)
    - Entry forms - Idealized Bodies program, 1995; 118714 (Box 8, Folder 749)
    - Entry forms - Jungli Boogie program, 1995; 118713 (Box 8, Folder 750)
    - Entry forms - No More Sweets for You program, 1995; 118712 (Box 8, Folder 751)
    - Entry forms - Omelette program, 1995; 118711 (Box 8, Folder 752)
    - Entry forms - Pornographic Imagination program, 1995; 118710 (Box 8, Folder 753)
    - Entry forms - Puppetoons: Dolls and Animation program, 1995; 118709 (Box 8, Folder 754)
    - Entry forms - Queer Family Skeletons program, 1995; 118708 (Box 8, Folder 755)
    - Entry forms - Rapture program, 1995; 118707 (Box 8, Folder 756)
    - Entry forms - Scorched Terrain: AIDS program, 1995; 118706 (Box 8, Folder 757)
    - Entry forms - Snow Queens program, 1995; 118705 (Box 8, Folder 758)
    - Entry forms - So Funny It Hurts program, 1995; 118704 (Box 8, Folder 759)
    - Entry forms - Vaginal Creme Davis Love Train program (CASSETTE and 2 7" RECORDS INCLUDED), 1995; 118703 (Box 8, Folder 760)
    - Entry forms - Vintage: Families of Value program, 1995; 118702 (Box 8, Folder 761)
    - Entry forms - Vulva Riot program, 1995; 118701 (Box 8, Folder 762)
    - Entry forms - Curatorial proposals, 1995; 118700 (Box 8, Folder 763)
    - Entry forms - Curatorial proposals, 1995; 118699 (Box 8, Folder 764)
    - Entry forms - Curatorial proposals ("originals"), 1995; 118698 (Box 8, Folder 765)
    - Entry forms - Installation applications, 1995; 118697 (Box 8, Folder 766)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by filmmaker's last name, A-F, 1995; 118696 (Box 9, Folder 767)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by filmmaker's last name, G-L, 1995; 118695 (Box 9, Folder 768)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by filmmaker's last name, M-R, 1995; 118694 (Box 9, Folder 769)
    - Entry forms - Rejected entries by filmmaker's last name, S-Z, 1995; 118693 (Box 9, Folder 770)
  - Subseries E: Press/Promotion/Posters (see also Oversize/Mapcase series), 118674
    - Artsnews - Mix 95 mention, 1995; 118691 (Box 9, Folder 772)
    - GiRl - "Fast Forward: Your Queer Movie Video Guide", 1995; 118690 (Box 9, Folder 773)
    - HX - "Hot 'n' Sticky? Vulva Riots? Snow Queens?", 1995; 118689 (Box 9, Folder 776)
    - HX - Mix mentions in Homo Musts and Linda Simpson's Drag Update, Mix 95 ad, 1995; 118688 (Box 9, Folder 777)
    - Knitting Factory Knotes - Schedule for Mix 95, 1995; 118687 (Box 9, Folder 778)
    - Metroline - "Going Celluloid with Mix 95", 1995; 118686 (Box 9, Folder 780)
    - Monitor - Mix 95 article, 1995; 118685 (Box 9, Folder 781)
    - New York - Mix mention in Cue: Movies section, 1995; 118684 (Box 9, Folder 782)
    - New York Press - Mix mention in "Calendar: November 1-7", 1995; 118683 (Box 9, Folder 783)
    - New York Times - Mix mention in Arts and Leisure section, 1995; 118682 (Box 9, Folder 784)
    - Screw - "The Gay's the Thing", 1995; 118681 (Box 9, Folder 785)
    - Time Out New York - Mix 95 Festival highlights and preview, 1995; 118680 (Box 9, Folder 786)
    - Village Voice - "Edgy, Sexy, Cool", 1995; 118679 (Box 9, Folder 788)
    - Afterparties - Flyers and information, 1995; 118678 (Box 9, Folder 789)
    - Afterparties - Hudson Grill flyer, 1995; 118677 (Box 9, Folder 790)
    - Mix 95 postcards, 1995; 118676 (Box 9, Folder 791)
    - Poster - designs, 1995; 118675 (Box 9, Folder 793)
  - Subseries F: Special Programs (see also Oversize series), 118665
    - A Different Take - Correspondence, 1995; 118673 (Box 9, Folder 795)
    - Black Nations/Queer Nations? - Project info and correspondence, 1995; 118672 (Box 9, Folder 797)
    - CEPA Gallery - Power and Desire off the Margins showcase, curated by Larry Brose - flyers, invoices, notes, 1995; 118671 (Box 9, Folder 798)
    - Cybertopia at Knitting Factory - Correspondence, 1995; 118670 (Box 9, Folder 800)
    - Mix Brasil - Correspondence, invoices, program listings, 1995-1996; 118669 (Box 9, Folder 801)
    - Mix Brussels - Correspondence, 1995; 118668 (Box 9, Folder 802)
    - Mix Magazine and Guia Mix, 1995; 118667 (Box 9, Folder 803)
    - Mix Sydney, 1995; 118666 (Box 9, Folder 804)
  - Subseries G: Media, 118471
    - Title: 607, Screened: [1995]; 118664 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0605)
      Director: Thompson, Walter
    - Title: Be Careful What Kind of Skin You Pull Back, You Never Know What Kind of Head Will Appear, Screened: 1994; 118663 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0606)
      Old number: 4
      Director: Bruning, Jurgen
    - Title: Naomi's Legacy, Screened: [1995]; 118662 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0607)
    - Title: Between These Few Silent Breaths, Screened: 1995; 118661 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0608)
      Director: Komisar, Lucinda
    - Title: Stolen Shadows, Screened: 1995; 118660 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0609)
      Old number: 9
      Director: Grandell, Steve and Killacky, John
    - Title: AIDS' Dark Terrain: Twelve Stations from a Yankee Pilgrim, Screened: [1995]; 118659 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0610)
      Director: Tichane, Robin
    - Title: [1.]--Ice Cream Sunday [2.]--Sexlock!, Screened: 1995; 118658 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0611)
      Director: [2.]--Cowan, Jeff
    - Title: Leather, Screened: 1995; 118657 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0612)
      Old number: 12
      Director: Haberman, Hardy
    - Title: Out for a change: Addressing homophobia in women's sports, Screened: [1995]; 118656 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0613)
      Distributor: additional credits: Woman Vision
    - Title: Eight, Screened: [1995]; 118655 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0614)
      Director: Gray, Elaine
    - Title: Intimate Relationships in Two Lesbian Families Living in American Society, Screened: [1995]; 118654 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0615)
      Director: [Asten, Dr. Maureen]
    - Title: What I'm Thinking, Screened: 1995; 118653 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0616)
      Director: Malaran, Barbara
    - Title: Personally Yours, Screened: 1995; 118652 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0617)
      Director: Robinson, Jeff
    - Title: Sherry Vine's Real, Screened: 1995; 118651 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0618)
      Director: Adam, Kevin
    - Title: Cowboy Jesus, Screened: 1995; 118650 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0619)
      Director: Yerkes, Jamie
    - Title: Days of Pentecost, Screened: 1995; 118649 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0620)
      Director: Elbert, Lawrence
    - Title: Borders, Screened: 1995; 118648 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0621)
      Old number: 24
      Director: Gelmini, Elio
    - Title: Out in South Africa, Screened: [1995]; 118647 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0622)
      Director: Hammer, Barbara
    - Title: Konichiwa Oldies, Screened: [1995]; 118646 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0623)
      Director: Sbrizzi, Paul
      Distributor: distributed by: Combo Productions
      Duration: 110 minutes
    - Title: Bottom, Screened: [1995]; 118645 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0624)
      Director: [Chiu, Terry]
    - Title: "Pull," a Portrait of David Nunsmaher, Screened: 1995; 118644 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0625)
      Old number: 29
      Director: Sherman, Stuart
    - Title: Letter To My Grandma, Screened: [1995]; 118643 (Box 111, Folder ID: 143.0626)
      Old number: 30
      Director: Howe, Alyssa Cymene
    - Title: Rocketlipsbabblon, Screened: 1995; 118642 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0627)
      Old number: 31
      Director: unknown
      Distributor: additional credits: AnnabelLee
    - Title: Same-Sex Marriages, Screened: [1995]; 118641 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0628)
      Director: Taria, Henrique
    - Title: Mummy, Screened: 1995; 118640 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0629)
    - Title: The Mild Ones, Screened: [1995]; 118639 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0630)
      Old number: 39, 505
      Director: Boccino, Joan
    - Title: Cum, Screened: 1995; 118638 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0631)
    - Title: A Day You Like, Screened: 1995; 118637 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0632)
      Old number: 41
      Director: Cornell, Clare Charles
    - Title: [1.]--A Day You Like [2.]--Grounded, Screened: [1995]; 118636 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0633)
      Old number: 42
    - Title: Exhibition, Screened: [1995]; 118635 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0634)
      Director: Lacey, Mark
    - Title: Sirocco, Screened: [1995]; 118634 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0635)
      Old number: 45
      Distributor: distributed by: Greenwood/Cooper Homevideo
    - Title: The Hygienic Mirror, Screened: [1995]; 118633 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0636)
      Director: [Gross, Brian]
    - Title: Truth or Hair?, Screened: [1995]; 118632 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0637)
      Director: Gross, Brian
    - Title: Guerita and Pretita, Screened: 1995; 118631 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0638)
      Director: High, Kathy and Shani Mootoo
    - Title: Her Sweetness Lingers, Screened: 1995; 118630 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0639)
      Director: Mootoo, Shani
    - Title: Her Sweetness Lingers, Screened: 1995; 118629 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0640)
    - Title: Get Happy or The Night Judy Garland Started a Riot, Screened: [1995]; 118628 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0641)
      Old number: 51
      Director: Bowes, Mark A.
    - Title: Desperation and Apparitions, Screened: 1995; 118627 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0642)
      Director: Alejandro, Pedro
    - Title: Novices, Screened: 1995; 118626 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0643)
      Director: Mau, Heidi and Thompson, Melissa
    - Title: [1.]--Emission [2.]--Comedie, [2.]--Screened: 1995; 118625 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0644)
      Old number: 54
      Director: [2.]--Henricks, Nelson
    - Title: but would you take her back?, Screened: [1995]; 118624 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0645)
      Director: Redding, Judith M.
    - Title: On Our Way to Hollywood, Screened: [1995]; 118623 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0646)
      Old number: 57
      Director: Keegan-Sommers, J.
    - Title: What To Put On Top of Jack Smith's Memorial Christmas Tree?, Screened: 1995; 118622 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0647)
      Old number: 58
      Director: Hayn, Stefan
    - Title: Snap Judgements #84: Von Praunheim's Express, Screened: 1995; 118621 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0648)
      Old number: 59
      Director: Ehmke, Ronald and Richard Wicka
    - Title: [1.]--Family Control [2.]--What Keeps [3.]--Camouflage Style [4.]--I Am Told, Screened: [1995]; 118620 (Box 112, Folder ID: 143.0649)
      Old number: 60
      Director: Steadman, Christopher
    - Title: Untitled Brad Hudson Mix 95 Entry, Screened: 1995; 118619 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0650)
      Old number: 61
      Director: Hudson, Brad
    - Title: Primary Process #1, Screened: 1995; 118618 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0651)
      Old number: 62
    - Title: Moscow Fags, Screened: [1995]; 118617 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0652)
      Distributor: distributed by: Poselski Brothers Moving Pictures
    - Title: Possession, Screened: 1995; 118616 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0653)
      Old number: 67
      Director: Nix, Laura
    - Title: Something About Me, Screened: [1995]; 118615 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0654)
      Old number: 68
    - Title: Butthole Bonanza, Screened: 1995; 118614 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0655)
      Old number: 69
      Director: Hughes, Todd
    - Title: Ding Dong, Screened: 1995; 118613 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0656)
      Old number: 70
    - Title: Batterer, Screened: 1995; 118612 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0657)
      Director: Parnes, Uzi
    - Title: Omelette, Screened: 1995; 118611 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0658)
      Director: Lange, Remi
    - Title: Hypothetical, Screened: 1995; 118610 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0659)
      Old number: 73
      Director: Endara, Lala
    - Title: [1.]--I Became a Lesbian and So Can You [2.]--The Housesitter [3.]--The Listener, Screened: [1995]; 118609 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0660)
      Old number: 74
      Director: Donahue, Lizzie
    - Title: [1.]--Cruising [2.]--Amazons [3.]--N.Y. Pier 34, Screened: [1995]; 118608 (E-records fales_mss143, E-records 143.0661, Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0661)
      Old number: 76
      Director: Domingo, Xavier
      Duration: 29 minutes
    - Title: Has Anybody Heard My Song, Screened: [1995]; 118607 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0662)
    - Title: In Suspect Terrain…, Screened: [1995]; 118606 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0663)
      Old number: 78
    - Title: Peach Melba, CP Kids, and The Queen of Bad TV, Screened: [1995]; 118605 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0664)
      Director: Caspersen, Randy
    - Title: You and I Will Play, Screened: [1995]; 118604 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0665)
      Old number: 80
      Director: Casperson, Randy
    - Title: Beyond Reason, Screened: [1995]; 118603 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0666)
      Old number: 81
      Director: Evangelista, Anton
    - Title: La Vie en Rose, Screened: 1993, 1995; 118602 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0667)
      Director: Boutte, Tony and Baker, James
    - Title: Swallow, Screened: 1995; 118601 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0668)
      Old number: 83
      Director: Subrin, Elisabeth
    - Title: Composition #1, Screened: [1995]; 118600 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0669)
      Director: Joseph, Gloria
    - Title: Oedipussy, Screened: 1995; 118599 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0670)
      Old number: 85
    - Title: Stranger Baby, Screened: 1995; 118598 (Box 113, Folder ID: 143.0671)
      Old number: 86
      Director: Lin, Lana
    - Title: [1.]--Forever Jimmy! [2.]--Screen Test, [1.]--Screened: 1995; 118597 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0672)
      Old number: 87
      Director: [1.]--Nguyen, Hoang Tan
    - Title: [1.]--Lesi Limericks and Queer Cheers [2.]--Three, By N. Furqueron [3.]--Bitch, Screened: 1995; 118596 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0673)
      Old number: 88
    - Title: Medicine Show, Screened: [1995]; 118595 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0674)
    - Title: FAG, Screened: [1995]; 118594 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0675)
      Old number: 90
    - Title: A Faustian Knot, Screened: 1995; 118593 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0676)
      Old number: 91
      Director: Chomont, Tom and Coleman, Clark
    - Title: Speaking for Ourselves: Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Youth, Screened: [1995]; 118592 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0677)
    - Title: Cut, Screened: 1993; 118591 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0678)
      Old number: 93
    - Title: Curiouser and Curiouser, Screened: 1995; 118590 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0679)
      Director: Izatt, Tracey
    - Title: I Confess, Screened: 1995; 118589 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0680)
    - Title: [1.]--Advent [2.]--Homunculus, [1.]--Screened: 1995; 118588 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0681)
      Director: [1.]--Roethlein, Terry
    - Title: Sunnybrook, Screened: 1995; 118587 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0682)
      Director: Blackbridge, Persimmon and Lorna Boschman
    - Title: Nice, Screened: 1995; 118586 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0683)
    - Title: Suspicious, Screened: 1995; 118585 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0684)
      Old number: 101
      Director: Thorne, Kika and Kelly O'Brien
    - Title: Whatever, Screened: [1995]; 118584 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0685)
      Old number: 102
      Director: Thorne, Kika
    - Title: Straight, No Chaser, Screened: 1995; 118583 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0686)
      Director: Rodriguez, Eugene
    - Title: The Origin of Her Virus, Screened: [1995]; 118582 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0687)
      Old number: 105
      Director: Link, Matthew
    - Title: Missing Relations, Screened: 1995, 1996; 118581 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0688)
      Old number: 107
    - Title: [1.]--Video Letter #1 [2.]--Video Letter #2 (or, call me an essentialist!) [3.]--Video Letter #3, Why would a letter have a title?, Screened: [1995]; 118580 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0689)
      Old number: 108
    - Title: In Your Hands, Screened: 1995; 118579 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0690)
      Director: Platt, Liss
    - Title: In Your Hands, Screened: 1995; 118578 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0691)
    - Title: I Shot My W.O.D., Screened: 1995; 118577 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0692)
      Director: Miller, Tanya and Wyman, Julie
    - Title: Designy Living, Screened: 1995; 118576 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0693)
      Old number: 115
      Director: Davis, Vaginal Crème
    - Title: Nocturne in E-Flat, Screened: [1995]; 118575 (Box 114, Folder ID: 143.0694)
      Director: Bump, Richard E.
    - Title: Skin-es-the-si-a, Screened: 1995; 118574 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0695)
      Old number: 119
      Director: Funari, Vicky
    - Title: STD CRY CIA, Screened: [1995]; 118573 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0696)
      Director: Thomas, Brett
    - Title: Idi, Screened: 1995; 118572 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0697)
      Old number: 122
      Director: Cutrone, Chris
    - Title: Lick, Screened: 1995; 118571 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0698)
      Director: Hima B and Eliza Barrios
    - Title: Detour, Screened: [1995]; 118570 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0699)
      Director: Twohatchet, Deron
    - Title: Peroden and Wisdom, Screened: [1995]; 118569 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0700)
    - Title: Stale Room, Screened: 1995; 118568 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0701)
      Director: Whang, Julie
    - Title: Can't Help Lovin Dat Man, Screened: 1995; 118567 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0702)
      Old number: 130
      Director: Umen, Alix and Prisco, Lisa
    - Title: Prague, Screened: [1995]; 118566 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0703)
    - Title: Gay Boy: We Do Not Go Extinct, Screened: [1995]; 118565 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0704)
      Old number: 139
      Director: Pollard, Aaron
    - Title: Coming Out of the Closet, Screened: [1995]; 118564 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0705)
      Director: Harman, Susan
    - Title: Re Generation, Screened: 1995; 118563 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0706)
    - Title: The Second Coming, Screened: 1996; 118562 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0707)
      Old number: 146
      Director: Walsh, Jack
    - Title: The Search, Screened: [1995]; 118561 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0708)
      Director: Morgan, Ben
    - Title: Political Funerals, Screened: [1995]; 118560 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0709)
      Old number: 153
    - Title: Sapphire and the Slave Girl (Excerpt), Screened: 1995, 1996; 118559 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0710)
      Director: Gilliam, Leah
    - Title: An Epic Falling Through the Cracks, Screened: 1995; 118558 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0711)
      Director: Andrews, Nancy
    - Title: I, Bear, Screened: 1995; 118557 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0712)
      Old number: 161
      Director: Mirra, Helen
    - Title: True Confessions of An Artist, Screened: 1995; 118556 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0713)
      Director: Stoltmann, Kirsten
    - Title: Swallow, Screened: 1995; 118555 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0714)
    - Title: 23 Minutes with NELSON, Screened: [1995]; 118554 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0715)
      Director: Sullivan, Nelson and Dick Richards
    - Title: [1.]--Crudite [2.]--Black-hair and Black-eyed, Screened: [1995]; 118553 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0716)
    - Title: It's A Love Story, Screened: 1995; 118552 (Box 115, Folder ID: 143.0717)
      Old number: 168
      Director: Running, Michael Rose
    - Title: The Pink, Screened: 1995; 118551 (Box 116, Folder ID: 143.0718)
      Old number: 169
    - Title: [1.]--…this [2.]-- pink [3.]-- 3 [4.]-- Land and Skin [5.]-- Postpartum Letter, [1, 2, 4, 5.]--Screened: 1995; 118550 (Box 116, Folder ID: 143.0719)
      Director: [1, 2.]--Konechne, Teresa [4, 5.]--Lin, Ju-Pong
    - Title: Cookies for Daddy, Screened: 1995; 118549 (Box 116, Folder ID: 143.0720)
      Director: Rasmussen, Melissa
    - Title: Cat Nip, Screened: 1995; 118548 (Box 116, Folder ID: 143.0721)
      Director: Taylor, Amanda
    - Title: Bodily Functions, Screened: 1995; 118547 (Box 116, Folder ID: 143.0722)
    - Title: Le Poisson D'Amour, Screened: 1995; 118546 (Box 116, Folder ID: 143.0723)
      Old number: 183
      Director: Gauthier, Paula
    - Title: Si…? Yeah!, Screened: 1995; 118545 (Box 116, Folder ID: 143.0724)
    - Title: Glenda and Camille Do Fashion Avenue, Screened: [1995]; 118544 (Box 116, Folder ID: 143.0725)
    - Title: Drag, Screened: 1995; 118543 (Box 116, Folder ID: 143.0726)